Step 1: click (550, 565) [OK]\NI can see the Google Flights page is loaded with a flight search form. The current setup shows 'Tokyo' as the departure
Step 2: click (556, 663) [OK]\NI can see the Google Flights page is loaded. Currently, the flight type dropdown shows 'Round trip' with a dropdown menu
Step 3: click (544, 565) [OK]\NI can see the Google Flights page is loaded with a search form. The current state shows 'Tokyo' as the departure city in
Step 4: click (960, 450) [OK]\NI can see the Google Flights page is loaded. Looking at the current state, I notice there's a dropdown menu visible show
Step 5: click (930, 619) [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see the Google Flights page is loaded. The departure city is already set to 'To
Step 6: find_and_type (1078, 640) [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see the Google Flights page with a search form. The departure city is already s
Step 7: click (1002, 729) [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see that I've already typed 'New York' in the destination field, and a dropdown
Step 8: click (961, 693) [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see the Google Flights page with the search form. The departure city is set to
Step 9: click (1113, 721) [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see the Google Flights page with a calendar open. The task requires me to searc
Step 10: click (1399, 1054) [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see the Google Flights page with a calendar open showing February and March. Th
Step 11: click (961, 693) [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see the Google Flights page is loaded with a search form. The departure city is
Step 12: scroll  [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see the Google Flights page with the search form. The departure city is set to
Step 13: done  [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see the Google Flights search results page showing flights from Tokyo (HND/NRT)